[
    {
        "question":"Do you have temper?",
        "answer":["Yes", "No"]
    },
    {
        "question":"Do you feel anxious frequently?",
        "answer":["Yes", "No", "Not Sure"]
    },
    {
        "question":"Do you feel sad often?",
        "answer":["Yes", "No"]
    },    
    {
        "question":"How frequently do you feel the sad?",
        "answer":["Multiple Times a day", "Once in a day","Few times a week", "Rarely"]
    },
    {
        "question":"Do you feel depressed?",
        "answer":["Yes", "No", "Not Sure"]
    },
    {
        "question":"Do you feel burnt out?",
        "answer":["No", "Only after excercise", "All the time"]
    },
    {
        "question":"Do you like stay alone lately?",
        "answer":["Yes", "No", "Sometimes"]
    },
    {
        "question":"If so then is it because of your mood swings?",
        "answer":["Yes", "No", "Maybe"]
    },
    {
        "question":"Do you socialize?",
        "answer":["Yes", "No", "I used to"]
    },
    {
        "question":"How often do you socialize?",
        "answer":["Atleast once a day", "Atleast once a week", "Atleast once a month", "Never"]
    },
    {
        "question":"Do you like socializing these days?",
        "answer":["Yes", "No", "Not Sure"]
    },
    {
        "question":"Have you had any feelings of self harming lately?",
        "answer":["Yes", "No", "Maybe"]
    },
    {
        "question":"Do you feel like ending yourself to solve health issues?",
        "answer":["Yes", "No", "Maybe"]
    },
    {
        "question":"Do you think you need help?",
        "answer":["Yes","No", "Maybe"]
    },
    {
        "question":"Do you talk to your family about your day?",
        "answer":["Yes","No", "Sometimes", "Not these days"]
    },
    {
        "question":"Do you have temper?",
        "answer":["Yes","No", "Maybe"]
    },
    {
        "question":"Do you feel anxious frequently?",
        "answer":["Yes","No","Not Sure"]
    }

]